const questionList = [
    {id: "1",
    question: "Which serial rugger rugged JellyBabiesNFT?",
    options: ["JellyPapa", "CarlosOMFGTv", "TurtleDice", "Syndicure"],
    answer: "JellyPapa"},
    {id: "2",
    question: "What was the JellyBabies initial mint price?",
    options: ["0.25 SOL", "0.1 SOL", "0.5 SOL", "0.15 SOL"],
    answer: "0.1 SOL"},
    {id: "3",
    question: "What was JellyEsports Alter-ego?",
    options: ["Carlos's angry side", "1 rascal + 500 $JELLY = new rascal", "Rascals got infected", "Light mode only on Discord"],
    answer: "1 rascal + 500 $JELLY = new rascal"},
    {id: "4",
    question: "What are Infected Rascals?",
    options: ["Wallet drainers", "A new collection of 'zombie' Rascals", "Rascals, but with COVID", "Rascals, but with ligma"],
    answer: "A new collection of 'zombie' Rascals"},
    {id: "5",
    question: "What is a Gambull?",
    options: ["Mutated JellyDawgs", "New NFT collection", "Online crypto casino", "Rascals with horns" ],
    answer: "Online crypto casino"},
    {id: "6",
    question: "How many GameRooms did you have to burn for a Rascal?",
    options: ["1", "5", "None", "2"],
    answer: "2"},
    {id: "7",
    question: "What does the no.1 ranked Rascal look like?",
    options: ["Golden armoured angel boi", "Monkey with eagle on head", "Astronaut", "Fortnite Ninja rascal"],
    answer: "Golden armoured angel boi"},
    {id: "8",
    question: "Who Wrote the Rascals Anthem?",
    options: ["TurtleDice", "MommaFlapz", "Alika Manuel", "KartelKulture"],
    answer: "Alika Manuel"},
    {id: "9",
    question: "What is a Rascals best friend?",
    options: ["Whiskey", "JellyDAWGS", "Diamonds", "Nobody"],
    answer: "JellyDAWGS"},
    {id: "10",
    question: "Which teams won the first JellyEsports DOA Battlepass?",
    options: ["Durags & Space", "WHD", "DINO", "LIGMA"],
    answer: "Durags & Space"},   
]

export {questionList}